A Guide to the Records of the Charlottesville School Board 1869-2006
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series X Deeds, Reports and Records
  - C. Records
    - Teacher Record Books, 1907-1970
      - Teacher Record Books M.L. Ballard-J. Wright 1917 Jun-Aug, 7 Items (Box-folder 100:3)
      - Teacher Record Books M.L. Ballard- T.I. Carter 1917-1918 Sep-Jan, 9 Items (Box-folder 100:4)
      - Teacher Record Books T.L. Cocke-A.A. Hankins 1917-1918 Sep-Jan, 10 Items (Box-folder 100:5)
      - Teacher Record Books W. Hayes- M.N. O'Rork 1917-1918 Sep-Jan, 8 Items (Box-folder 100:6)
      - Teacher Record Books L.A. Parrish-S. Rothwell 1917-1918 Sep-Jan, 7 Items (Box-folder 101:1)
      - Teacher Record Books M.K. Thacker-J. Wright 1917-1918 Sep-Jan, 7 Items (Box-folder 101:2)
      - Teacher Record Books D.M. Allan-F. Cocke 1918 Feb-May, 9 Items (Box-folder 101:3)
      - Teacher Record Books R.E. Cocke-W.J. Hayes 1918 Feb-May, 10 Items (Box-folder 101:4)
      - Teacher Record Books A.O. Hawkins-M. Morris 1918 Feb-May, 9 Items (Box-folder 101:5)
      - Teacher Record Books M.N. O'Rork- S. Rothwell 1918 Feb-May, 7 Items (Box-folder 101:6)
      - Teacher Record Books M.K. Thacker-J.Wright 1918 Feb-May, 9 Items (Box-folder 102:1)
      - Teacher Record Books A.Ballard-M.J. Blakely 1918-1919 Sep-Jan, 9 Items (Box-folder 102:2)
      - Teacher Record Books A.E. Bloxton-B. Dolan 1918-1919 Sep-Jan, 9 Items (Box-folder 102:3)
      - Teacher Record Books E.H. Edmunds-M.E. Monroe 1918-1919 Sep-Jan, 10 Items (Box-folder 102:4)
      - Teacher Record Books S.A. Moran-E.H. Smith 1918-1919 Sep-Jan, 8 Items (Box-folder 102:5)
      - Teacher Record Books L. Snyder-J.Wright 1918-1919 Sep-Jan, 8 Items (Box-folder 102:6)
      - Teacher Record Books A.E. Bloxton-S.A. Moran 1918 Jun-Aug, 3 Items (Box-folder 103:1)
      - Teacher Record Books Term Reports 1918, 32 Items (Box-folder 103:2)
      - Teacher Record Books Term Reports 1919,1920, 15 Items (Box-folder 103:3)
      - Teacher Record Books Mc-S 1919-1926, Part ½ (Box-folder 103:4)
      - Teacher Record Books S-Z 1919-1926, Part ½ (Box-folder 103:5)
      - Teacher Record Books A.E. Ballard-M.Bryant 1919 Feb-May, 9 Items (Box-folder 103:6)
      - Teacher Record Books M.Burnley-E.H. Edmunds 1919 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 103:7)
      - Teacher Record Books L.A. Gerard-M.E. Monroe 1919 Feb-May, 9 Items (Box-folder 104:1)
      - Teacher Record Books S.A. Moran-E.H. Smith 1919 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 104:2)
      - Teacher Record Books M.J. Sullivan-J. Wright 1919 Feb-May, 7 Items (Box-folder 104:3)
      - Teacher Record Books A. Ballard- J. Wright 1919 Jun-Aug, 9 Items (Box-folder 104:4)
      - Teacher Record Books Term Reports 1919-1920, 36 Items (Box-folder 104:5)
      - Teacher Record Books E.B. Allbritten-S.C. Blasingame 1919-1920, 8 Items (Box-folder 104:6)
      - Teacher Record Books E.J. Brown-A.L. Crawford 1919-1920 Sep-Jan, 8 Items (Box-folder 105:1)
      - Teacher Record Books B.Dolan-H.S. Harris 1919-1920 Sep-Jan, 8 Items (Box-folder 105:2)
      - Teacher Record Books H.S. Harris-S.A. Moran 1919-1920 Sep-Jan, 8 Items (Box-folder 105:3)
      - Teacher Record Books. J.A. Morrow-E. Rubush 1919-1920 Sep-Jan, 8 Items (Box-folder 105:4)
      - Teacher Record Books M. Scriber-P.V. Willoughby 1919-1920 Sep-Jan, 8 Items (Box-folder 105:5)
      - Teacher Record Books E.B. Allbritten-S.C. Blasingame 1920 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 105:6)
      - Teacher Record Books E.J. Brown-B. Dolan 1920 Feb-May, 9 Items (Box-folder 106:1)
      - Teacher Record Books C. Garrett-V.K. Karmes 1920 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 106:2)
      - Teacher Record Books J.A. Morrow-E. Rubush 1920 Feb-May, 9 Items (Box-folder 106:3)
      - Teacher Record Books M. Scriber-J. Wright 1920 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 106:4)
      - Teacher Record Books M.L. Ballard-M.N. O'Rork 1920 Jun-Aug, 7 Items (Box-folder 106:5)
      - Teacher Record Books M.N. O'Rork-J. Wright 1920 Jun-Aug, 6 Items (Box-folder 106:6)
      - Teacher Record Books Term Reports 1920-1921, 63 Items (Box-folder 107:1)
      - Teacher Record Books R.P. Abell-S.C. Blasingame 1920-1921 Sep-Jan, 9 Items (Box-folder 107:2)
      - Teacher Record Books M. Brooks- J.M. Cane 1920-1921 Sep-Jan, 7 Items (Box-folder 107:3)
      - Teacher Record Books R.E. Cooke-C. Garrett 1920-1921 Sep-Jan, 8 Items (Box-folder 107:4)
      - Teacher Record Books V. Gorrell-R. Kimbrough 1920-1921 Sep-Jan, 8 Items (Box-folder 107:5)
      - Teacher Record Books W.E. Lacy-P.A. Payne 1920-1921 Sep-Jan, 8 Items (Box-folder 107:6)
      - Teacher Record Books E.A. Peyton-L.G. Snider 1920-1921 Sep-Jan, 7 Items (Box-folder 107:7)
      - Teacher Record Books F-W 1920-1921 Sep-Jan, 8 Items (Box-folder 108:1)
      - Teacher Record Books R. P. Abell-D.L. Blakey 1921 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 108:2)
      - Teacher Record Books S.C. Blasingame-BMR Feaganes 1921 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 108:3)
      - Teacher Record Books R.M. Fuller-R.L. Kimbraugh 1921 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 108:4)
      - Teacher Record Books W.E. Lacy-S.E. Rubush 1921 Feb-May, 9 Items (Box-folder 108:5)
      - Teacher Record Books L.G. Snider-J. Wright 1921 Feb-May, 7 Items (Box-folder 108:6)
      - Teacher Record Books E. Atkins-W.E. Lacy 1921 Jun-Aug, 7 Items (Box-folder 109:1)
      - Teacher Record Books E.B. Payne-J. Wright 1921 Jun-Aug, 5 Items (Box-folder 109:2)
      - Teacher Record Books A.B. Adams- S.C. Blasingame 1921-1922 Sep-Jan, 9 Items (Box-folder 109:3)
      - Teacher Record Books M. Brooks-A. Crawley 1921-1922 Sep-Jan, 9 Items (Box-folder 109:4)
      - Teacher Record Books A.M. Cross-J.C. Jones 1921-1922 Sep-Jan, 9 Items (Box-folder 109:5)
      - Teacher Record Books V. Jones-M.N. O'Rork 1921-1922 Sep-Jan, 9 Items (Box-folder 109:6)
      - Teacher Record Books M.N. O'Rork-S.E. Rubush 1921-1922 Sep-Jan, 8 Items (Box-folder 110:1)
      - Teacher Record Books J.H. Snapp-J. Wright 1921-1922 Sep-Jan, 7 Items (Box-folder 110:2)
      - Teacher Record Books A.B. Adams-M. Burnley 1922 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 110:3)
      - Teacher Record Books M. Brooks-B. Dolan 1922 Feb-May, 9 Items (Box-folder 110:4)
      - Teacher Record Books L.W. Eisenberg-J.C. Jones 1922 Feb-May, 9 Items (Box-folder 110:5)
      - Teacher Record Books J.C. Jones- M.N. O'Rork 1922 Feb-May, 10 Items (Box-folder 110:6)
      - Teacher Record Books M.N. O'Rork-R. Risner 1922 Feb-May, 9 Items (Box-folder 111:1)
      - Teacher Record Books L. Rowlett-L.G. Snider 1922 Feb-May, 6 Items (Box-folder 111:2)
      - Teacher Record Books A.L. Stone-J. Wright 1922 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 111:3)
      - Teacher Record Books M.L. Ballard-A. Cross 1922 Jun-Aug, 9 Items (Box-folder 111:4)
      - Teacher Record Books R.M. Fuller- J. Wright 1922 Jun-Aug, 9 Items (Box-folder 111:5)
      - Teacher Record Books Term Reports 1922-1923, 27 Items (Box-folder 111:6)
      - Teacher Record Books A.B. Adams-A.W. Barringer 1922-1923 Sep-Jan, 8 Items (Box-folder 111:7)
      - Teacher Record Books Term reports 1922-1923, # items (Box-folder 112:1)
      - Teacher Record Books D.L. Blakey-A.W. Cross 1922-1923 Sep-Jan, 9 Items (Box-folder 112:2)
      - Teacher Record Books A.W. Cross-E. Matthews 1922-1923 Sep-Jan, 9 Items (Box-folder 112:3)
      - Teacher Record Books E. McClung-E.A. Peyton 1922-1923 Sep-Jan, 8 Items (Box-folder 112:4)
      - Teacher Record Books E.A. Peyton-J.H. Snapp 1922-1923 Sep-Jan, 9 Items (Box-folder 112:5)
      - Teacher Record Books L.G. Snider-J. Wright 1922-1923 Sep-Jan, 9 Items (Box-folder 112:6)
      - Teacher Record Books Term Reports 1923-1924, 29 Items (Box-folder 113:1)
      - Teacher Record Books Term Reports 1923-1924, 27 Items (Box-folder 113:2)
      - Teacher Record Books A.B. Adams- D.L. Blakey 1923 Feb-May, 9 Items (Box-folder 113:3)
      - Teacher Record Books D.L. Blakey-M. Burnley 1923 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 113:4)
      - Teacher Record Books A. Crawley-R.M. Darden 1923 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 113:5)
      - Teacher Record Books R.M. Darden-E. McClung 1923 Feb-May, 9 Items (Box-folder 113:6)
      - Teacher Record Books E. McClung-E.A. Peyton 1923 Feb-May, 9 Items (Box-folder 113:7)
      - Teacher Record Books R.Risher-M.E. Shackelford 1923 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 114:1)
      - Teacher Record Books N.P. Sheppe-M.E. Sutherland 1923 Feb-May, 6 Items (Box-folder 114:2)
      - Teacher Record Books M.K. Thacker-J. Wright 1923 Feb-May, 6 Items (Box-folder 114:3)
      - Teacher Record Books R.M. Fuller-J. Wright 1923 Jun-Aug, 9 Items (Box-folder 114:4)
      - Teacher Record Books E. Atkins-M.W. Burwell 1923-1924 Sep-Jan, 8 Items (Box-folder 114:5)
      - Teacher Record Books M.W. Burwell-A.M. Cross 1923-1924 Sep-Jan, 8 Items (Box-folder 114:6)
      - Teacher Record Books F.J. Daniels-M.E. Green 1923-1924 Sep-Jan, 8 Items (Box-folder 115:1)
      - Teacher Record Books N.B. Huyett-E.B. Payne 1923-1924 Sep-Jan, 9 Items (Box-folder 115:2)
      - Teacher Record Books M.L Quarles-M. Taliaferro 1923-1924 Sep-Jan, 9 Items (Box-folder 115:3)
      - Teacher Record Books M.L. Taliaferro-V. Venable 1923-1924 Sep-Jan, 7 Items (Box-folder 115:4)
      - Teacher Record Books J.K. Werner-J. Wright 1923-1924 Sep-Jan, 7 Items (Box-folder 115:5)
      - Teacher Record Books Midway High Summary for 1 st-2 nd Year Students 1923-1924 Sep-Jan, 6 Items (Box-folder 115:6)
      - Teacher Record Books Midway High Summary for 2 nd-4 th Year Students 1923-1924 Sep-Jan, 6 Items (Box-folder 115:7)
      - Teacher Record Books E. Atkins-S. Craft 1924 Feb-May, 9 Items (Box-folder 116:1)
      - Teacher Record Books C. Crawley-C.A. Gable 1924 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 116:2)
      - Teacher Record Books M.E. Green-E.B. Payne 1924 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 116:3)
      - Teacher Record Books E.B. Payne-M. Stratton 1924 Feb-May, 7 Items (Box-folder 116:4)
      - Teacher Record Books L. Stradler-T.H. Taylor 1924 Feb-May, 5 Items (Box-folder 116:5)
      - Teacher Record Books M. Torrence-J. Wright 1924 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 116:6)
      - Teacher Record Books Midway High Summary for 1 st-4 th Year Students 1924 Feb-May, 10 Items (Box-folder 116:7)
      - Teacher Record Books E. Atkins-J. Wright 1924 Jun-Aug, 9 Items (Box-folder 117:1)
      - Teacher Record Books Term Reports 1924-1925, 24 Items (Box-folder 117:2)
      - Teacher Record Books Term Reports 1924-1925, 22 Items (Box-folder 117:3)
      - Teacher Record Books Term Reports 1924-1925, 18 Items (Box-folder 117:4)
      - Teacher Record Books E. Atkins-M.L. Burnley 1924-1925 Sep-Jan, 7 Items (Box-folder 117:5)
      - Teacher Record Books S. Craft-R.M. Fuller 1924-1925, 7 Items (Box-folder 117:6)
      - Teacher Record Books M.E. Griffith- W.S. Long 1924-1925, 6 Items (Box-folder 117:7)
      - Teacher Record Books E.B. Payne-M.E. Sutherland 1924-1925, 7 Items (Box-folder 117:8)
      - Teacher Record Books E.S. Bennett-M.L. Burnley 1924 Feb-May, 9 Items (Box-folder 118:1)
      - Teacher Record Books M.L. Burnley-H. Early 1924 Feb-May, 9 Items (Box-folder 118:2)
      - Teacher Record Books L.W. Eisenberg-M.P. Kite 1924 Feb-May, 10 Items (Box-folder 118:3)
      - Teacher Record Books T. Taylor-L.P. Woodson 1924-1925, 7 Items (Box-folder 118:4)
      - Teacher Record Books H.A.-D.B. Yancey 1924-1925, 3 Items (Box-folder 118:5)
      - Teacher Record Books C.G. Lilly-S. Moore 1925 Feb-May, 9 Items (Box-folder 118:6)
      - Teacher Record Books S. Moore-M.E. Shackelford 1925 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 118:7)
      - Teacher Record Books N.P. Sheppe-M.V. Taliaferro 1925 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 119:1)
      - Teacher Record Books T. Taylor-L.S. Yancey 1925 Feb-May, 10 Items (Box-folder 119:2)
      - Teacher Record Books D.L. Blakey-H.H. Walker 1925 Jun-Aug, 10 Items (Box-folder 119:3)
      - Teacher Record Books Term Reports 1925-1926, 5 Items (Box-folder 119:4)
      - Teacher Record Books C.C. Britzer-R.E. Hines 1925-1926 Sep-Jan, 11 Items (Box-folder 119:5)
      - Teacher Record Books R.E. Hines-J. Wright 1925-1926 Sep-Jan, 12 Items (Box-folder 119:6)
      - Teacher Record Books R.P. Abell-R.M. Jones 1926 Feb-May, 6 Items (Box-folder 120:1)
      - Teacher Record Books E.B. Hiedebrand-R.C. Wingfield 1926 Feb-May, 12 Items (Box-folder 120:2)
        Includes 1925-1926 Report Cards from [Dama] Hill
      - Teacher Record Books E. Atkins-R.C. Wingfield 1926 June-Aug, 8 Items (Box-folder 120:3)
      - Teacher Record Books V.N. Clore-R.E. Hines 1926-1927 Sep-Jan, 6 Items (Box-folder 120:4)
      - Teacher Record Books L.T. Jones-E. Scribner 1926-1927 Sep-Jan, 7 Items (Box-folder 120:5)
      - Teacher Record Books M.B. Summers-L.S. Yancey 1926-1927 Sep-Jan, 7 Items (Box-folder 120:6)
      - Teacher Record Books Term Reports-Midway High 1926-1927, 61 Items (Box-folder 120:7)
      - Teacher Record Books A.L. Berrey-M.P. Kite 1927 Feb-May, 7 Items (Box-folder 121:1)
      - Teacher Record Books W.S. Long-S.C. Speidel 1927 Feb-May, 6 Items (Box-folder 121:2)
      - Teacher Record Books M.B. Summers-L.S. Yancey 1927 Feb-May, 9 Items (Box-folder 121:3)
      - Teacher Record Books E. Atkins-W.S. Long 1927 Jun-Aug, 6 Items (Box-folder 121:4)
      - Teacher Record Books D. Phillips-R.C. WIngfield 1927 Jun-Aug, 5 Items (Box-folder 121:5)
      - Teacher Record Books A.L. Berrey-M.P. Kite 1927-1928 Sep-Jan, 9 Items (Box-folder 121:6)
      - Teacher Record Books W.S. Long-R.E. Stine 1927-1928 Sep-Jan, 8 Items (Box-folder 121:7)
      - Teacher Record Books M.E. Sutherland-L.S. Yancey 1927-1928 Sep-Jan, 6 Items (Box-folder 121:8)
      - Teacher Record Books Term Reports-Midway 1927-1928, 82 Items (Box-folder 122:1)
        Includes 9 Teacher's Inspection Reports
      - Teacher Record Books A.L. Berrey-R.E. Hines 1928 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 122:2)
      - Teacher Record Books L.T. Jones-N.P Sheppe 1928 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 122:3)
      - Teacher Record Books Y.C. Speidel-L.S. Yancey 1928 Feb-May, 7 Items (Box-folder 122:4)
      - Teacher Record Books E. Atkins-H.N. Fuller 1928 Jun-Aug, 7 Items (Box-folder 122:5)
      - Teacher Record Books M.S. Shackelford-R.C. Wingfield 1928 Jun-Aug, 7 Items (Box-folder 122:6)
      - Teacher Record Books A.L. Berrey-M.C. Jones 1928-1929, 7 Items (Box-folder 123:1)
      - Teacher Record Books E.C. Mason-S.C. Speidel 1928-1929, 7 Items (Box-folder 123:2)
      - Teacher Record Books M.E. Sutherland-A.S. Young 1928-1929, 8 Items (Box-folder 123:3)
      - Teacher Record Books Term Reports 1928-1929, 74 Items (Box-folder 123:4)
        Including 8 Classification of Pupil Forms from 1929
      - Teacher Record Books A.L. Berrey-E.B. Payne 1929, 8 Items (Box-folder 123:5)
      - Teacher Record Books N.P. Sheppe-A.S. Young 1929, 9 Items (Box-folder 123:6)
      - Teacher Record Books E. Atkins-G. Ulepatry 1929 Jun-Aug, 5 Items (Box-folder 124:1)
      - Teacher Record Books A.B. Adams-V.N. Clore 1929-1930 Sep-Jan, 9 Items (Box-folder 124:2)
      - Teacher Record Books M.W. Duke-S.P. Horwitz 1929-1930 Sep-Jan, 9 Items (Box-folder 124:3)
      - Teacher Record Books. W. Johnston-L. Nickels 1929-1930 Sep-Jan, 10 Items (Box-folder 124:4)
      - Teacher Record Books E.B. Payne-M.W. Sims 1929-1930 Sep-Jan, 10 Items (Box-folder 124:5)
      - Teacher Record Books S.C. Speidel-J.K. Werner 1929-1930 Sep-Jan, 6 Items (Box-folder 124:6)
      - Teacher Record Books Term Reports-McGuffey 1929-1930, 64 Items (Box-folder 125:1)
      - Teacher Record Books Term Reports Berry-Yancey 1929-1930, 50 items (Box-folder 125:2)
      - Teacher Record Books McGuffey A.B. Adams-A. Burnet 1930 Feb-May, 5 items (Box-folder 125:3)
      - Teacher Record Books Buruss-Luck 1930 Feb-May, 4 items (Box-folder 125:4)
      - Teacher Record Books M.V. Forbes-R. Kice 1930 Feb-May, 6 items (Box-folder 125:5)
      - Teacher Record Books Hewson-Wilkes 1929-1930 Sep-Jun, 5 items (Box-folder 125:6)
      - Teacher Record Books Berry-Jones 1929-1930, 5 items (Box-folder 125:7)
      - Teacher Record Books Brown-McConnell 1929-1930, 5 items (Box-folder 125:8)
      - Teacher Record Books Woodson-Young 1930 Feb-May, 6 items (Box-folder 125:9)
      - Teacher Record Books L. Nickels-N.P. Sheppe 1930 Feb-May, 7 Items (Box-folder 126:1)
      - Teacher Record Books M.L. Sims-H.H. Walker 1930 Feb-May, 7 Items (Box-folder 126:2)
      - Teacher Record Books J.K. Werner- A.S. Young 1930 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 126:3)
      - Teacher Record Books E. Atkins-M.E. Kelly 1930 Jun-Aug, 7 Items (Box-folder 126:4)
      - Teacher Record Books M. Shackelford-A.S. Young 1930 Jun-Aug, 7 Items (Box-folder 126:5)
      - Teacher Record Books Summer-Midway High School 1930 Jun-Aug, 5 Items (Box-folder 126:6)
      - Teacher Record Books- Term Reports 1930-1931, 11 Items (Box-folder 127:1)
      - Teacher Record Books A.B. Adams-I.L. Boston 1930-1931 Sep-Jan, 7 Items (Box-folder 127:2)
      - Teacher Record Books L.W. Brown-E.M. Burruss 1930-1931 Sep-Jan, 7 Items (Box-folder 127:3)
      - Teacher Record Books M. Burnet- Johnson 1930-1931 Sep-Jan, 6 Items (Box-folder 127:4)
      - Teacher Record Books J. Jones-D. Persinger 1930-1931 Sep-Jan, 7 Items (Box-folder 127:5)
      - Teacher Record Books E.W. Pettit-H. Sadler 1930-1931 Sep-Jan, 6 Items (Box-folder 127:6)
      - Teacher Record Books G. Schuder-J.K. Werner 1930-1931 Sep-Jan, 6 Items (Box-folder 127:7)
      - Teacher Record Books L.P. Woodson-L.S. Yancey 1930-1931 Sep-Jan, 6 Items (Box-folder 128:1)
      - Teacher Record Books- Term Reports 1930-1931, 56 Items (Box-folder 128:2)
      - Teacher Record Books A.B. Adams-A. Browne 1931 Feb-May, 6 Items (Box-folder 128:3)
      - Teacher Record Books A. Browne- E. Burruss 1931 Feb-May, 6 Items (Box-folder 128:4)
      - Teacher Record Books M.W. Duke-T. Gochenour 1931 Feb-May, 6 Items (Box-folder 128:5)
      - Teacher Record Books W. Johnston-S. Moore 1931 Feb-May, 7 Items (Box-folder 128:6)
      - Teacher Record Books S. Moore-M.G. Quarles 1931 Feb-May, 6 Items (Box-folder 128:7)
      - Teacher Record Books M.G. Quarles-M.L. Sims 1931 Feb-May, 6 Items (Box-folder 129:1)
      - Teacher Record Books M.L. Sims-A.S Young 1931 Feb-May, 6 Items (Box-folder 129:2)
      - Teacher Record Books E. Atkins-M.E. Kelly 1931 Jun-Aug, 5 Items (Box-folder 129:3)
      - Teacher Record Books- Office 1930-1931, 9 Items (Box-folder 129:4)
      - Teacher Record Books D. Blakely 1931-1932 Sep-Jan, 6 Items (Box-folder 129:5)
      - Teacher Record Books J. Jones-H.L. Sadler 1931-1932 Sep-Jan, 6 Items (Box-folder 129:6)
      - Teacher Record Books H.L. Sadler-A.S. Young 1931-1932 Sep-Jan, 7 Items (Box-folder 130:1)
      - Teacher Record Books D. Blakey-T. Gochenour 1932 Feb-May, 7 Items (Box-folder 130:2)
      - Teacher Record Books T.V. Gochenour-D. Persinger 1932 Feb-May, 7 Items (Box-folder 130:3)
      - Teacher Record Books H.L. Sadler-L.P. Woodson 1932 Feb-May, 7 Items (Box-folder 130:4)
      - Teacher Record Books E.M. Atkins-M. Trevillian 1932 Jun-Aug, 6 Items (Box-folder 130:5)
      - Teacher Record Books D. Blakey-Burruss 1932-1933 Sep-Jan, 6 Items (Box-folder 130:6)
      - Teacher Record Books E.M. Burruss-S. Moore 1932-1933 Sep-Jan, 7 Items (Box-folder 131:1)
      - Teacher Record Books M.H. Trevillian-L.P Woodson 1932-1933 Sep-Jan, 7 Items (Box-folder 131:2)
      - Teacher Record Books D. Blakey-M. Burnet 1933 Feb-May, 7 Items (Box-folder 131:3)
      - Teacher Record Books E. Burruss-S.Moore 1933 Feb-May, 8 Items (Box-folder 131:4)
      - Teacher Record Books J.V. Gochenour-L.P. Woodson 1933 Feb-May, 7 Items (Box-folder 131:5)
      - Teacher Record Books M. Boudin-M.B Whitlock 1933 Jun-Aug, 4 Items (Box-folder 131:6)
      - Teacher Record Books I.D. Sinclair-L.P. Woodson 1933-1934 Sep-Jan, 5 Items (Box-folder 132:1)
      - Teacher Record Books H.S. Burnley-E. Crenshaw 1933-1934 Sep-Jan, 8 Items (Box-folder 132:2)
      - Teacher Record Books D. Blakey-M.B. Burnet 1934 Feb-May, 6 Items (Box-folder 132:3)
      - Teacher Record Books M.G. Fitzhugh-S. Moore 1934 Feb-May, 7 Items (Box-folder 132:4)
      - Teacher Record Books G. Shufflebarger-L.P. Woodson 1934 Feb-May, 7 Items (Box-folder 132:5)
      - Teacher Record Books M. Burnet-G. Deputy 1934 Jun-Aug (Box-folder 132:6)
      - Teacher Record Books D. Blakey-E. Crenshaw 1934-1935 Sep-Jan, 7 Items (Box-folder 133:1)
      - Teacher Record Books M.G. Fitzhugh-G. Shufflebarger 1934-1935 Sep-Jan, 6 Items (Box-folder 133:2)
      - Teacher Record Books I.D. Sinclair-L.P. Woodson 1934-1935 Sep-Jan, 5 Items (Box-folder 133:3)
      - Teacher Record Books D. L. Blakey-H.S. Burnley 1935 Feb-May, 6 Items (Box-folder 133:4)
      - Teacher Record Books E.M. Burruss-S. Moore 1935 Feb-May, 7 Items (Box-folder 133:5)
      - Teacher Record Books G.S. Shufflebarger-L.P. Woodson 1935 Feb-May, 6 Items (Box-folder 133:6)
      - Teacher Record Books D. Blakey-H.S. Burnley 1935-1936 Sep-Jan, 6 Items (Box-folder 134:1)
      - Teacher Record Books E.M. Burness-E.P. Marchant 1935-1936 Sep-Jan, 6 Items (Box-folder 134:2)
      - Teacher Record Books G. Shufflebarger-L.P. Woodson 1935-1936 Sep-Jan, 6 Items (Box-folder 134:3)
      - Teacher Record Books D. Blakey-E.M. Burness 1936 Feb-May, 6 Items (Box-folder 134:4)
      - Teacher Record Books E. Crenshaw-N. Waddell 1936 Feb-May, 4 Items (Box-folder 134:5)
      - Teacher Record Books M.G. Fitzhugh-L.P. Woodson 1936 Feb-May, 7 Items (Box-folder 134:6)
      - Teacher Record Books Term Reports 1936-1937, 34 Items (Box-folder 135:1)
      - Teacher Record Books A.L. Barksdale-E.M. Burruss 1936-1937 Sep-Jan, 7 Items (Box-folder 135:2)
      - Teacher Record Books E. Crenshaw-S. Moore 1936-1937 Sep-Jan, 6 Items (Box-folder 135:3)
      - Teacher Record Books G. Shufflebarger-L.P. Woodson 1936-1937 Sep-Jan, 6 Items (Box-folder 135:4)
      - Teacher Record Books A.L. Barksdale-E.M. Burness 1937 Feb-May, 7 Items (Box-folder 135:5)
      - Teacher Record Books E. Crenshaw-G. Shufflebarger 1937 Feb-May, 6 Items (Box-folder 135:6)
      - Teacher Record Books I.D. Sinclair-L.P. Woodson 1937 Feb-May, 5 Items (Box-folder 135:7)
      - Teacher Record Books Term Reports 1937-1938, 38 Items (Box-folder 136:1)
      - Teacher Record Books A.B. Adams-H.S. Burnley 1937-1938 Sep-Jan, 6 Items (Box-folder 136:2)
      - Teacher Record Books H.S. Burnley-C. Phillips 1937-1938 Sep-Jan, 6 Items (Box-folder 136:3)
      - Teacher Record Books M.A. Quarles-L.P. Woodson 1937-1938 Sep-Jan, 6 Items (Box-folder 136:4)
      - Teacher Record Books A.B. Adams-H.S. Burnley 1938 Feb-May, 6 Items (Box-folder 136:5)
      - Teacher Record Books N. W. Cote-M.A. Quarles 1938 Feb-May, 6 Items (Box-folder 136:6)
      - Teacher Record Books G.S. Shufflebarger-L.P. Woodson 1938 Feb-May, 5 Items (Box-folder 136:7)
      - Teacher Record Books A.B. Adams-M.B. Burnet 1938-1939 Sep-Jan, 4 Items (Box-folder 137:1)
      - Teacher Record Books H.S Burnley-T. Gochenour 1938-1939 Sep-Jan, 4 Items (Box-folder 137:2)
      - Teacher Record Books M.L. Duerson-C. Phillps 1938-1939 Sep-Jan, 4 Items (Box-folder 137:3)
      - Teacher Record Books M.A. Quarles-L.P. Woodson 1938-1939 Sep-Jan, 5 Items (Box-folder 137:4)
      - Teacher Record Books A.B. Adams-I.W. Boston 1939 Feb-May, 4 Items (Box-folder 137:5)
      - Teacher Record Books M. Burnet-M.T. Duenson 1939 Feb-May, 4 Items (Box-folder 137:6)
      - Teacher Record Books T. Gochenour-M.A. Quarles 1939 Feb-May, 4 Items (Box-folder 138:1)
      - Teacher Record Books G. Shufflebarger-L.P. Woodson 1939 Feb-May, 4 Items (Box-folder 138:2)
      - Teacher Record Books A.B. Adams-M.B. Burnet 1939-1940 Sep-Jan, 5 Items (Box-folder 138:3)
      - Teacher Record Books H.S. Burnley-N.W. Cole 1939-1940 Sep-Jan, 5 Items (Box-folder 138:4)
      - Teacher Record Books G. Shufflebarger-L.P. Woodson 1939-1940 Sep-Jan, 4 Items (Box-folder 138:5)